## Hello

## I'm Jordan Bryant

597 N. Holliston Ave Pasadena, CA 91106 (323) 540-7703 jsbrymail@gmail.com jordanbryant.design

## About me

I have 6+ years experience designing for digital platforms including iOS & Android mobile, web and television. My client list includes A24, AT&T, Cablevision, Directv, Lionsgate, Microsoft, Mitsubishi, Sony, Southern California Edison, Universal and Warner Bros.

# Experience

MAR 2017-PRESENT

**Possible**—Playa Vista, CA—Freelance Senior UI Designer

SEP 2016-MAR 2017

Iconmobile—Santa Monica, CA—Freelance Senior UI Designer

MAR 2015-SEP 2016

Concept Arts—Hollywood, CA—Digital Art Director

JUN 2014-MAR 2015

**Directv**—El Segundo, CA—Ul Designer

DEC 2013-MAY 2014

**Possible**—Culver City, CA—Designer

NOV 2011-DEC 2013

**Schematic**—Culver City, CA—Associate Designer

## Education

AUG 2013

California State University Northridge, Northridge, CA—B.A. in Art & Graphic Design

#### Skills

UI/UX & product design, prototyping, motion, front-end dev, print design, typography, illustration.

## **Tools**

Sketch, Figma, Principle, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Adobe Creative Suite.